Guide to Barbara Sloan European Union Document Collection, 1951-2004 EUDC
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- POLICY AREA, II.
  - EXTERNAL RELATIONS, 13.
    - ASIA
      - Afghanistan [441.2(311)], 1979-2004; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 154)
      - Bhutan [441.2(313)], 2003; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 154)
      - Burma/Myanmar [441.2(314)], 1988-2003; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 154)
      - Cambodia [441.2(315)], 1979-2003; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 154)
      - Sri Lanka [441.2(316)], 1994-2003; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 154)
      - China [441.2(317)], 1964-2000; 8.; 2 folders 9" (Box 154)
      - Korea [441.2(319)], 1971-2003; 9.; 1 folder 3" (Box 156)
      - India and Pakistan [441.2(321+332)], 1962-2003; 10.; 2 folders 10" (Box 156)
      - Indonesia [441.2(322) ], 1981-2003; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 157)
      - Japan [441.2(326)], 1964-1987; 12.; 5 folders 25" (Box 159, Box 160)
      - Malaysia [441.2(329)], 1981-2004; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 161)
      - Nepal [441.2(330)], 1982-2002; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 161)
      - Mongolia [441.2(331)], 1992-2003; 15.; 1 folder 1" (Box 162)
      - Philippines [441.2(333)], 1982-2002; 16.; 1 folder 1" (Box 162)
      - Thailand [441.2(335)], 1981-2002; 17.; 1 folder 1" (Box 162)
      - Vietnam [441.2(337)], 1974-2003; 18.; 1 folder 1" (Box 164)
      - Yemen North and South [441.2(338)], 1983-2003; 19.; 1 folder 1" (Box 164)
      - Hong Kong [441.2(339)], 1970-2003; 20.; 1 folder 1" (Box 164)
      - Bangladesh [441.2(340)], 1984-2002; 21.; 1 folder 1" (Box 164)
      - Macao [441.2(341)], 1992-2002; 22.; 1 folder 1" (Box 164)
      - Laos [441.2(342)], 1987-2002; 23.; 1 folder 1" (Box 164)
      - East Timor [441.2(343)], 2002-2003; 24.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 164)
    - WESTERN EUROPE
      - Austria [441.2(44)], 1958-1989; 1.; 3 folders 10" (Box 114)
      - Cyprus [441.2(318)], 1962-2003; 2.; 3 folders 10" (Box 155)
      - Spain [441.2(47)], 1970-1985; 3.; 5 folders 17" (Box 115, Box 116)
      - Finland [441.2(48)], 1970-2000; 4.; 1 folder 6" (Box 117)
      - United Kingdom [441.2(51)], 1961-1972; 5.; 4 folders 15" (Box 117)
      - Greece [441.2(53)], 1959-1981; 6.; 5 folders 18" (Box 119)
      - Ireland [441.2(55)], 1961-1972; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 121)
      - Iceland [441.2(56)], 1970-2003; 8.; 1 folder 4" (Box 122)
      - Monaco [441.2(59)], 1963-2003; 9.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 122)
      - Portugal [441.2(62)], 1970-2003; 10.; 3 folders 10" (Box 123)
      - Denmark [441.2(66)], 1961-1992; 11.; 1 folder 3" (Box 127)
      - Norway [441.2(67)], 1962-2003; 12.; 2 folders 9" (Box 127)
      - Sweden [441.2(68)], 1972-1994; 13.; 2 folders 8" (Box 128)
      - Switzerland [441.2(69)], 1962-2003; 14.; 3 folders 17" (Box 128, Box 129)
      - Malta [441.2(72)], 1970-2003; 15.; 2 folders 7" (Box 134)
      - Faroe Islands (1981 on) [441.2(73)], 1980-2002; 16.; 1 folder (Box 135)
      - Andorra [441.2(74)], 1985-2003; 17.; 1 folder 1" (Box 135)
      - Liechtenstein [441.2(75)], 1991-2003; 18.; 1 folder 1" (Box 135)
      - San Marino [441.2(76)], 1986-2003; 19.; 1 folder 1" (Box 135)
    - FOREIGN POLICY, SECURITY POLICY AND DEFENSE
      - Disarmament [327.37], 1967-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 8)
      - Foreign Ministers Conference on Political Cooperation (Davignon Committee) [420.43], 1970-1983; 2.; 4 folders 17" (Box 54)
      - European Defence Community Treaty [489.1], 1952; 3.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 376)
      - Defense, European Integration [420.41], 1967-2003; 4.; 2 folders 4" (Box 52)
      - Common Foreign & Security Policy CFSP - General [441.5], 1992-2003; 5.; 1 folder 4" (Box 165)
      - Common Foreign & Security Policy Declarations - General [441.51], 1995-2003; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 165)
      - Common Foreign & Security Policy - Joint Actions [441.52], 1994-2003; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 165)
      - Sanctions, European Union Actions Common Foreign & Security Policy [441.53], 1989-2003; 8.; 1 folder 4" (Box 166)
      - Common Foreign & Security Policy - Background Briefing Notes - Confidential [441.54], 1994-1997; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 166)
      - Common Foreign & Security Policy - Institutional Arrangements [441.55], 2000-2002; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 166)
      - Common Foreign & Security Policy - Conflict Prevention/Crisis Management [441.56], 2001-2003; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 166)
    - RESEARCH & TECHNOLOGY, INTERNATIONAL COOPERATION
      - Scientific Technical & Nuclear Affairs, International Aspects [441.4], 1959-2003; 1.; 2 folders 5" (Box 165)
  - EXTERNAL TRADE, 14.
    - EXTERNAL TRADE General
      - EXTERNAL TRADE General [4411], 1970-2003; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 297)
    - COMMERCIAL POLICY GENERAL
      - Commercial Policy, ARTICLE 113 Special Committee [4411.01], 1970-2002; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 297)
      - Commercial Policy General [4411.1], 1960-2003; 2.; 1 folder 4" (Box 297)
      - Commercial Policy, Agricultural Trade [4411.2], 1960-1999; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 304)
      - Commodity Agreements, International (See Individual Commodities for Specifics) [4411.21], 1966-1990; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 304)
      - International Organizations, Commercial Policy Relations with [4411.3], 1970-2002; 5.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 304)
      - National Trade Agreements, Commercial Policy (See also Individual Countries in 441.2) [4411.4], 1969-2001; 6.; 1 folder 4" (Box 304)
    - COMMERCIAL POLICY INSTRUMENTS
      - Safeguard Clause (See also 431-Article 226) Commercial Policy [4411.11], 1963-1984; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 297)
      - Export Promotion Commercial Policy [4411.12], 1971-1997; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 297)
      - Credit Insurance, Commercial Policy [4411.13], 1971-2002; 3.; 2 folders 7" (Box 298)
      - Import Quotas Pre-Liberalization List Member State [4411.14], 1964-1995; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 298)
      - Import Arrangements, Common [4411.15], 1965-2003; 5.; 3 folders 16" (Box 298)
      - Commercial Policy, New Instruments [4411.151], 1983-2004; 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 299)
      - Dumping, Common Commercial Policy [4411.16], 1965-2004; 7.; 8 folders 35" (Box 300, Box 301, Box 302, Box 303)
      - Export Arrangements, Common Commercial Policy [4411.17], 1969-2002; 8.; 1 folder 2" (Box 303)
      - European Export Bank [4411.171], 1975-1994; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 303)
      - Export Controls; Coordinating Committee for Multilateral Export Controls (COCOM) Dual Use Technology [4411.172], 1989-2003; 10.; 1 folder 9" (Box 303)
      - Trade Restrictions - Non Tariff Trade Barriers [337.5], 1969-2000; 11.; 1 folder 3" (Box 13)
    - TRADE NEGOTIATIONS
      - General Agreement on Trade and Tariffs (GATT) General [411], 1955-2003; 1.; 2 folders 3" (Box 40)
      - GATT Dillon Round [411.1], 1960-1964; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 41)
      - GATT Kennedy Round 1962 & 1963 [411.3], 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 42)
      - GATT Kennedy Round 1964 [411.3], 4.; 1 folder 2" (Box 42)
      - GATT Kennedy Round 1965 [411.3], 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 42)
      - GATT Kennedy Round 1966 [411.3], 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 42)
      - GATT Kennedy Round 1967 [411.3], 7.; 1 folder 3" (Box 43)
      - GATT Kennedy Round 1968 [411.3], 1968-1972; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 43)
      - GATT Kennedy Round (Special) [411.3], 1966; 9.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 43)
      - GATT Kennedy Round Post -1968 [411.3], 1969-1974; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 43)
      - GATT Multilateral Trade Negotiations 1972 -1979 [411.4], 11.; 4 folders 11" (Box 43)
      - GATT Tokyo Round Post Multilateral Trade Negotiations [411.5], 1980-1989; 12.; 2 folders 5" (Box 44)
      - GATT Uruguay Round [411.6], 1984-2002; 13.; 4 folders 17" (Box 45)
      - GATT Uruguay Round Rapid Reports [411.61], 1988-1990; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 46)
      - GATT World Trade Organization (WTO) Post Uruguay Round [411.7], 15.; 1 folder 6" (Box 46)
      - World Trade Organization (WTO) Millennium Round [411.8], 1999-2003; 16.; 1 folder 3" (Box 47)
  - INDUSTRIAL AFFAIRS, 15.
    - INDUSTRIAL AFFAIRS General
      - INDUSTRIAL AFFAIRS General [443], 1977-2001; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 175)
      - Industrial Policy & Studies [443.01], 1967-2003; 2.; 4 folders 19" (Box 175, Box 176, Box 177)
      - Small & Medium-Sized Industry Crafts [443.012], 1961-2003; 3.; 4 folders 13" (Box 177)
      - International Multilateral Corporation [338.961], 1972-2001; 4.; 2 folders 8" (Box 14)
      - Public Enterprise General [351.824.11], 1967-2003; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 24)
      - Business Cooperation Centre [443.013], 1968-1999; 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 178)
      - Internal Market Program 1992 [443.014], 1985-2003; 7.; 4 folders 17" (Box 179)
    - STEEL General
      - STEEL General [443.2], 1963-2003; 1.; 12 folders 40" (Box 188, Box 189, Box 190, Box 191)
      - Steel, General Objectives [443.21], 1971-1990; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 191)
      - Steel, Production Supply & Raw Materials [443.22], 1972-1984; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 192)
      - Steel scrap [443.221], 1969-1996; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 192)
      - Iron Ore [443.222], 1969-1985; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 192)
      - Steel, Market Controls; Together with "Steel, Market Analysis & Forecasts" [443.23], 1969; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 192)
      - Steel, Market Analyses & Forecasts; Together with "Steel, Market Controls" [443.24], 1973; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 192)
    - INDUSTRY SECTORS & APPLICATIONS
      - INDUSTRY SECTORS & APPLICATIONS [443.3], 1970-1990; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 192)
      - Industries, Specific Overview [443.31[, 1959-1987; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 192)
      - Beer Industry [443.311], 1962 - 1986; 3.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 192)
      - Broadcasting/Radio/Television [654.1], 1962 & 1986; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 406)
      - Chemical Industry [443.311], 1981-2003; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 192)
      - Construction Industry [443.311], 1975-1999; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 192)
      - Defense Industry [443.311], 1975-2003; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 192)
      - Food Industry [664], 1969-1998; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 408)
      - Electronic Industry (Including Data Processing) [443.311], 1971-1998; 9.; 2 folders 7" (Box 192)
      - Leather & Shoes Industry [443.311], 1973-2000; 10.; 1 folder 2" (Box 193)
      - Mail Order Business [658.872], 1972-1983; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 407)
      - Metals & Machine Tools Industry [443.311], 1963-1994; 12.; 1 folder 2" (Box 193)
      - Optical & Precision Instruments Industry [443.311], 1972-1978; 13.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 193)
      - Paper & Pulp Industry [443.311], 1968-2000; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 193)
      - Rubber Industry [443.311], 1981-1985; 15.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 193)
      - Ship Building Industry [443.311], 1963-2003; 16.; 3 folders 9" (Box 193)
      - Telecommunications Services [654.1], 1962-2003; 17.; 3 folders 12" (Box 406, Box 404, Box 405)
      - Textiles Industry [443.311], 1959-2003; 18.; 2 folders 5" (Box 194)
      - Tourism [380.8], 1961-2003; 19.; 2 folders 10" (Box 29)
      - Nuclear Energy, Industrial Applications of [443.32], 1966-1985; 20.; 1 folder 3" (Box 195)
      - Bureau EURISOTOP; Measures to Improve Existing and Introduce New Techniques in Industry [443.34], 1965-1984; 21.; 1 folder 2" (Box 195)
  - INTERNAL MARKET & HARMONIZATION OF LEGISLATION, 16.
    - INTERNAL MARKET & HARMONIZATION OF LEGISLATION - General
      - INTERNAL MARKET & HARMONIZATION OF LEGISLATION - General [4414], 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 315)
      - Internal Market Program 1992 [443.014], 1985-2003; 2.; 4 folders 17" (Box 179)
      - Consumer Policy and Protection [339.41], 1965-2003; 3.; 4 folders 16" (Box 15)
    - RIGHT OF ESTABLISHMENT & SERVICES
      - RIGHT OF ESTABLISHMENT & SERVICES [4414.1], 1959-2003; 1.; 2 folders 6" (Box 315)
      - Right of Establishment - Industry Commerce Crafts Agriculture & Transport [4414.11] (Folder Missing), 2. (Box 315)
      - Accountants, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1970-1996; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Agriculture & Forestry, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1963-1990; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Art & Artists, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1964-2000; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Banking & Financial Institutions, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1965-1985; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Cinematography, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1963-1981; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Commercial Agents, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1976-1996; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Corporations, Right of Establishment (See 4414.23 Company Law) [4414.111] (Folder Missing), 9. (Box 316)
      - Electricity Gas Water & Sanitary Services (Self-Employed Persons) [4414.111], 1964 & 1983; 10.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 316)
      - Food & Beverages (Self-Employed Persons) Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1965-1987; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Hairdressers, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1971-1996; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Manufacturing Activities Industrial & Artisan (Self-Employed Persons) Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1963-1985; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Mining & Quarrying (Self Employed) Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1963 & 1967; 14.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 316)
      - Non-Salaried Activities Miscellaneous, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1967-1985; 15.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Petroleum & Natural Gas, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1967-1985; 16.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Pharmaceutical Industry, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1967-2000; 17.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Press, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1964-1983; 18.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Real Estate & Business Services, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1964-1987; 19.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Restaurants & Hotels, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1965-1985; 20.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Retail Trade, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1965-1980; 21.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
      - Sports, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1971-2002; 22.; 1 folder 2" (Box 316)
      - Toxic Products, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1969-1974; 23.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 316)
      - Transport, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1970-2003; 24.; 1 folder 3" (Box 316)
      - Wholesale Trade & Intermediate Occupations, Right of Establishment [4414.111], 1963-1983; 25.; 1 folder 1" (Box 316)
    - RIGHT OF ESTABLISHMENT, PROFESSIONS
      - RIGHT OF ESTABLISHMENT, PROFESSIONS; Installation in a Member State in Order to Pursue Economic Activity [4414.12], 1968-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 316)
      - Architects, Right of Establishment [4414.121], 1967-2003; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 317)
      - Dental Profession, Right of Establishment [4414.121], 1965-2000; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 317)
      - Engineers, Right of Establishment [4414.121], 1969-1991; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 317)
      - Lawyers, Right of Establishment [4414.121], 1969-2000; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 317)
      - Medical Profession, Right of Establishment (See also 4414.111 Pharmaceutical) [4414.121], 1969-2002; 6.; 2 folders 5" (Box 317)
      - Veterinarians, Right of Establishment [4414.121], 1970-1998; 7.; 1 folders 1" (Box 317)
    - FINANCIAL SERVICES, General
      - FINANCIAL SERVICES, General [4414.2], 1978-2003; 1.; 1 folder 1 (Box 317)
      - Banks (332.1 in Library Catalog) [4414.21], 1970-2003; 2.; 5 folders 19" (Box 318)
      - Insurance (368 in Library Catalog) [4414.22], 1962-2003; 3.; 4 folders 15" (Box 319, Box 320)
      - Securities & Exchange Systems [4414.25], 1972-2003; 4.; 3 folders 16" (1 folder missing) (Box 323)
      - Committee of European Securities Regulators [4414.251], 2002; 5.; 1 folder 1-2 documents (Box 324)
    - COMPANY LAW
      - IM: Company law, Banks, Insurance General [4414.2], 1978-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 317)
      - Company Law [4414.23], 1964-2003; 2.; 5 folders 16" (Box 321)
      - European Economic Interest Group [4414.231], 1976-1997; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 322)
      - European Company Statute [4414.24], 1965-2003; 4.; 2 folders 8" (Box 322)
      - Consultation of Workers, Vredling proposal [445.311], 1978-2002; 5.; 1 folder 5" (Box 218)
      - International Multilateral Corporation [338.961], 1972-2001; 6.; 2 folders 8" (Box 14)
    - HARMONIZATION OF LAW AND PRODUCT STANDARDS
      - HARMONIZATION OF LAW AND PRODUCT STANDARDS [4413.3], 1960-2003; 1.; 4 folders 12" (Box 312)
      - Harmonization of Law General [4414.31], 1972-1997; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 326, Box 325)
      - Aerosols and Fluorocarbons Ozone [4414.311], 1973-2003; 3.; 1 folder 4" (Box 326)
      - Agricultural Tractors and Machinery [4414.311], 1966-2003; 4.; 2 folders 5" (Box 327)
      - Ceramic Ware [4414.311], 1974-1984; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 327)
      - Chains & Cables [4414.311], 1971-2003; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 327)
      - Chemicals, Regulation (See Dangerous Substances) [4414.311] (Folder Missing), 7. (Box 327)
      - Compressors [4414.311], 1978-1985; 8.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 327)
      - Construction Equipment and Materials [4414.311], 1974-2003; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 327)
      - Consumer Contracts [4414.311], 1991-2003; 10.; 1 folder 2" (Box 327)
      - Consumer Credit [4414.311], 1979-2003; 11.; 1 folder 2" (Box 328)
      - Contract Law [4414.311], 2001-2003; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 328)
      - Cosmetics [4414.311], 1972-2003; 13.; 1 folder 6" (Box 328)
      - Crystal Glass [4414.311], 1968-1984; 14.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 328)
      - Dangerous Substances [4414.311], 1965-2004; 15.; 7 folders 31" (Box 328, Box 329, Box 330)
      - Detergents [4414.311], 1971-2003; 16.; 1 folder 1" (Box 329)
      - Domestic Appliances [4414.311], 1978-2003; 17.; 2 folders 1" (Box 331)
      - Door-to-Door Selling [4414.311], 1976-1986; 18.; 1 folder 1" (Box 331)
      - Driving Regulations [4414.311], 1977-2003; 19.; 1 folder 2" (Box 331)
      - Electrical Component & Instrumentation [4414.311], 1965-2003; 20.; 1 folder 6" (Box 331)
      - Elevators [4414.311], 1975-2000; 21.; 1 folder 1" (Box 332)
      - Explosives [4414.311], 1992-2003; 22.; 1 folder 1" (Box 332)
      - Fertilizer [4414.311], 1971-2003; 23.; 1 folder 3" (Box 332)
      - Gambling [4414.311], 1991-1998; 24.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 332)
      - Lawnmowers [4414.311], 1978-1998; 25.; 1 folder 1" (Box 332)
      - Machine Tools and Similar Machines [4414.311], 1977-1996; 26.; 1 folder 1" (Box 332)
      - Machines [4414.311], 1987-2003; 27.; 1 folder 3" (Box 333)
      - Marine Equipment [4414.311], 1995-2003; 28.; 1 folder 1" (Box 333)
      - Measuring Instruments [4414.311], 1966-2002; 29.; 2 folders 6" (Box 333)
      - Medical Devices [4414.311], 1990-2003; 30.; 1 folder 4" (Box 333)
      - Motor Vehicles [4414.311], 1965-2003; 31.; 7 folders 36" (Box 334, Box 335, Box 336)
      - Motorcycles [4414.311], 1973-2002; 32.; 1 folder 3" (Box 334)
      - Non-Electrical Appliances [4414.311], 1975-1989; 33.; 1 folder 1" (Box 337)
      - Personal Protective Equipment [4414.311], 1988-2001; 34.; 1 folder 1" (Box 337)
      - Petroleum Products [4414.311], 1971-2003; 35.; 1 folder 5" (Box 337)
      - Pharmaceutical Products [4414.311], 1961-2003; 36.; 5 folder 18" (Box 339, Box 338)
      - Pipelines (See 388.5) [4414.311], 1962-2003; 37.; 3 folders 18" (Box 339)
      - Power-Driven Tools [4414.311], 1964-1982; 38.; 1 folder 1" (Box 339)
      - Precautionary Principle (See Product Safety) [4414.311], 1979-2003; 39.; 1 folder 2" (Box 339)
      - Precious Metals [4414.311], 1975-2001; 40.; 1 folder 1" (Box 339)
      - Pressurized Containers [4414.311], 1973-2003; 41.; 1 folder 2" (Box 339)
      - Product Liability [4414.311], 1974-2003; 42.; 1 folder 3" (Box 339)
      - Product Safety [4414.311], 1979-2003; 43.; 1 folder 2" (Box 339)
      - Product Standards, Miscellaneous [4414.311], 1967-1998; 44.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 334)
      - Recreational Craft (See Ships and Boats) [4414.311], 1968-2003; 45.; 1 folder 2" (Box 339)
      - Safety Signs [4414.311], 1976-1991; 46.; 1 folder 1" (Box 339)
      - Textiles, Harmonization of Law [4414.311], 1969-1997; 47.; 1 folder 1" (Box 339)
      - Time; Zones - common "summertime" in Member States [389.2], 1968-2004; 48.; 1 folder 1" (Box 39)
      - Toys [4414.311], 1977-2003; 49.; 1 folder 2" (Box 340)
      - Weights and Measures [389.1], 1979-2003; 50.; 1 folder 2" (Box 39)
      - European Agency for Medicinal Products [4414.312], 1994-2002; 51.; 1 folder 1" (Box 340)
    - PATENTS & INTELLECTURAL PROPERTY
      - Patents - Industrial Property [4414.32], 1959-2003; 1.; 5 folders 18" (Box 340, Box 341, Box 342)
      - Trademarks [4414.32], 1959-2003; 2.; 5 folders 18" (Box 342)
      - Trademarks, Design, Office for Harmonization [4414.321], 1993-2003; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 342)
      - Procurement Public Works Contracts [4414.33], 1965-2003; 4.; 4 folders 18" (Box 342, Box 343)
    - ADVERTISING
      - Advertising [4414.34], 1965-2003; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 344)
    - TAXATION, General
      - TAXATION, General [4414.4], 1958-2003; 1.; 2 folders 7" (Box 344)
      - Harmonization of Taxes. Tax Bases. Double Imposition [4414.41], 1966-2003; 2.; 1 folder 4" (Box 345)
      - Value Added Taxes [4414.411], 1966-2003; 3.; 1 folder 4" (Box 347)
      - Turnover Taxes [4414.411], 1961-2004; 4.; 5 folders 21" (Box 345, Box 346)
      - Excise Taxes [4414.412], 1972-2003; 5.; 2 folders 9" (Box 348)
      - Company Taxation [4414.413], 1969-2003; 6.; 1 folder 4" (Box 348)
      - Competition, Elimination of Tax Distortions [4414.42], 1971-2001; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 348)
      - Circulation of Merchandise, Elimination of Tax Distortions [4414.421], 1967-2002; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 348)
      - Capital Movements, Elimination in [4414.422], 1965-2003; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 348)
      - Capital Markets, Elimination of [4414.423], 1964-2003; 10.; 1 folder 2" (Box 349)
  - INTERNATIONAL COMMODITIES & AGREEMENTS, 17.
    - COMMODITY AGREEMENTS, INTERNATIONAL (See Individual Commodities for Specific Agreements)
      - COMMODITY AGREEMENTS, INTERNATIONAL (See Individual Commodities for Specific Agreements) [382.4: 63], 1969-1986; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 31)
      - Commodity Agreements, International (See Individual Commodities for Specifics) [4411.21], 1966-1990; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 304)
    - BASIC PRODUCTS
      - Raw Materials [338.1], 1974-2000; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 13)
      - Bananas, World [6(CST 051.3)(1)], 1966-1982; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 383)
      - Beef, World [6(CST 011.1)(1)], 1967-1988; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 380)
      - Cereals, World 6(CST 04)(1)], 1962-2003; 4.; 1 folder 4" (Box 383)
      - Coal, Europe [6(CST 32)(20)], 1964-1968; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)
      - Coal, United States [6(CST 32)(103)], 1957-1981; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)
      - Cocoa, World [6(CST 072)(1)], 1966-2002; 7.; 1 folder 3" (Box 384)
      - Coffee, World [6(CST 071)(1)], 1968-2001; 8.; 1 folder 4" (Box 384)
      - Copper, World [6(CST 283.1)(1)], 1977-1991; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)
      - Dairy Products, World [6(CST 02)(1)], 1967-1988; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 380)
      - Fertilizers, World [6(CST 56)(1)], 1967-1982; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)
      - Fish and Fish Products, World [6(CST 03)(1)], 1976-2003; 12.; 6 folders 29" (Box 380, Box 381, Box 382)
      - Jute, World [6(CST 653.4)(1)], 1977-2002; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 388)
      - Lead & Zinc, World [6(CST 283.4)(1)], 2001; 14.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 385)
      - Leather Hides & Skins World [6(CST 21)(1)], 1972-2001; 15.; 1 folder 1" (Box 384)
      - Nickel, World [6(CST 683)(l)], 1991; 16.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 388)
      - Oils & Fats, World [6(CST 22)(1)], 1969-2003; 17.; 1 folder 2" (Box 384)
      - Petroleum, World [6(CST 33)(1)], 1969-1978; 18.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)
      - Rubber, World [6(CST 23)(1)], 1977-2002; 19.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)
      - Sugar, World [6(CST 06)(1)], 1967-2003; 20.; 1 folder 3" (Box 383)
      - Tea, World [6(CST 074)(1)], 1976-1980; 21.; 1 folder 1" (Box 384)
      - Tin, World [6(CST 687)(1)], 1970-1995; 22.; 1 folder 2" (Box 388)
      - Tobacco, World [6(CST 12)(1)], 1963-2003; 23.; 1 folder 2" (Box 384)
      - Wood & Cork, World [6(CST 24)(1)], 1967-2003; 24.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)